A Guide to the Miscellaneous Genealogical Notes Collection No. 26., 2009
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Miscellaneous Genealogical Notes Collection No. 26., 2009
The Library of Virginia
52842
.35 cu. ft. and 1 box
Virginia Daughters of the American Revolution
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the Virginia Daughters of the American Revolution
Scope and Content
Includes Bible records, cemetery records, death records, genealogies, land records, marriage records, obituaries, and wills relating to the following families: Allemang, Brooks, Brown, Clark, Coble, Coleman, Deems, Dickinson, Embrey, Fogleman, Graves, Hageloch, Horn, Irwin, Isley, Lay, Lilly, Logan, Loyd, Martin, McBroom, Morrison, Nunns, Osborne, Pemberton, Reed Stafford, Streit, Thomas, and Ware. Localities covered include: Fauquier and Spotsylvania Counties, and Alexandria and Winchester, Virginia; and Germany, Illinois, Maryland, Mississippi, New York, North Carolina, Ohio, Texas, and West Virginia. Includes biographical information on John C. Pemberton (1814-1881) and historical information on Andrews Tavern, Spotsylvania County. Includes index.
Contents List
- Front material (3 pages) (Folder 1)
- Copiah County, Mississippi marriage bonds, 1831(pp. 1-3) (Folder 2)
- The Nunns family of New York City (pp. 4-43) (Folder 3)
- Allemang, Horn Logan, Clark family Bible record (Adams, Highland, and Pike Counties, Ohio), 1781-1958 (pp. 44-59) (Folder 4)
- Irwin, Osborne, Ware families marriage records, obituaries, (Fayette, Montgomery, and Sangamon Counties, Illinois), 1832-1931 (pp. 60-76) (Folder 5)
- Hageloch family Bible record (Germany), 1806-1897 (pp. 77-80) (Folder 6)
- Irwin, McBroom families marriage records (Sangamon County, Illinois), 1897 (pp. 81-83) (Folder 7)
- Martin family genealogical notes (Rochester, New York) (pp. 84-95) (Folder 8)
- Brooks, Brown, Embrey families genealogical notes (Fauquier County, Virginia) (pp. 96-175) (Folder 9)
- McBroom, Osborne families marriage records, death records, petition (Montgomery and Shelby Counties, Illinois), 1854-1927 (pp. 176-183) (Folder 10)
- Deems family death records (Alexandria, Virginia), 1946-1954 (pp. 184-185) (Folder 11)
- Lay, Lilly families marriage records, death records (Baltimore, Maryland), 1900-1932 (pp. 186-188) (Folder 12)
- Graves, Isley families, genealogical notes (Orange County, North Carolina) (pp. 189-207) (Folder 13)
- Monongalia, Monroe, and Pendleton Counties, West Virginia, marriage records, 1807-1880 (pp. 208-221) (Folder 14)
- Fogleman, Graves, Isley, Stafford, Coble families marriage records, death record (Guilford and Orange Counties, North Carolina, and Baltimore, Maryland), 1806-1898 (222-235 pp.) (Folder 15)
- Reed family death records, will (Monroe and Monongalia Counties, West Virginia), 1845-1893 (pp. 236-238) (Folder 16)
- Coble family wills (Orange County, North Carolina), 1846 (pp. 239-240) (Folder 17)
- Reed, Osborne, McBroom, Ware, Irwin families genealogical notes (Champaign and Montgomery Counties, Illinois), (pp. 241-263) (Folder 18)
- Upshur County, Texas land records, 1850-1907 (pp. 264-303) (Folder 19)
- Morrison, Thomas, Pemberton, Loyd, Dickinson, families genealogical notes (Spotsylvania County, Virginia) (pp. 304-327) (Folder 20)
- Streit family genealogical notes (pp. 328-334) (Folder 21)
- Dickinson, Coleman families Bible records, obituaries (Spotsylvania County, Virginia) 1804-1967 (pp. 335-345) (Folder 22)
- Andrews Tavern (Spotsylvania County, Virginia) (pp. 346-359) (Folder 23)
- John C. Pemberton (pp. 360-363) (Folder 24)
- Index (26 p.) (Folder 25)